Welcome back ladies and gentlemen to the Intel Extreme Masters type pay we are nearing the end of day one in control
How are you feeling how are you feeling now just about Starcraft? How are you feeling in general? Thank you. I appreciate that
Have a little bit of a cold and like I said, I'm I'm on East Coast time zone right now
But even that's weird and when you have only been on one cruise in my life just got back from a cruise which is amazing really fun
But actually for like a day or two you still feel the sway of the boat. Yeah, which is weird
You know what that makes you Jeff what imbalanced
To start snoot versus hero ladies and gentlemen our last best of five of the evening we are loaded in
To dust towers you didn't expect that did you I didn't
Smotting in the bottom left representing team liquid we have snoot who you're looking he says G. L. H. F
I don't know why he said question mark. Yeah, interesting. He's still on Casper rules when he's don't see anything
I can't talk right. I can't speak to me the last time I spoke to someone it was to save him from being disqualified
Maybe that's right. You know, I met by the way of course. It's CJ Antis hero in the Northeast the smiling assassin
Does he ever say G. L. H. F. is opponent doesn't say it? That's a question. Is that like is it like programmed and maybe programmed into your brain?
You're if you're in Casper well, I would so cool about these guys is they are a lot of those Casper guys tops your friends
No and play with each other so much that that kind of stuff doesn't really matter to them
There's no BM either way they can say anything. We're just playing games. Okay. Well
No, this isn't the safe space. We have to say G. L. H. F. and no, that's not what I'm saying
It is that's super serious business for them, but it's just this is one game of like 40 they played that week against that guy
So when hero doesn't say it to soul here something like that. There's no do they hate you now
They either can't or they don't care because they're gonna they're gonna laugh and high five and rub each other's shoulders in 10 minutes because they're like best friends
All right, well
Tell me about some pvz. What are your experiences?
You have a double-hatch full-play from smooth everyone I've been talking to pretty much generally
Complains with the last patch. It's hard to deal with early lane aggression, but I guess this map is probably the best map for defending
Yeah, it feels like I feel like part of the reason why this matchup is particularly difficult for us right now is because
Zerg finally got that go between unit the ravager that is really good offensively decent enough defensively not super expensive and has transition
It's not you're not punished if you're stuck on 10 ravagers. They actually have an effect they have they have
Efficacy all the way to the end of the game so they're really good that way
Mutus very powerful stargate hard to punish because of the speed of the game if you open up stargate
It was always true and hard to form too you had to do decent damage if you didn't you're in a lot of trouble
But all of a sudden because of the power of things like lurkers and the deep power of things like colossus
You don't have that amazing unit to fall back on that can kind of make up the difference between you and tech pass
So it's funny to think about it is not like the heart of the swarm colossus could actually probably still truck most
Zerg armies in this game most armies in general yeah
I mean it was like it was the it was the unit for anti-ground and it was
It was it was a bad unit it's funny to think about it
And I do enjoy as I get commentator in a player obviously as a player I enjoy not seeing colossus
I but as a as a spectator watching non-college this games I find any more fun
Fastly more interesting and that was the problem is they were too good
So they were they were just prevalent all three matchups and they demanded that you responded them with your text
Voice because if you didn't hardcore deal with them they would just dominate truck over so that's why they were bad
And blizzard agrees that they became has kind of always been pretty vocal about that. I'm glad that sort of you know the end game
GG units like that have kind of been taking out a little bit at least is something said in this matchup
I agree
I maybe maybe some product players would argue with me on the count of like lurkers being strong as well
But some players have some of the guys that I've talked to you have said that there are some compositions that people have been
Playing with more that have helped a lot against the those styles
I think people been saying like zealot arc on can kind of just better better down on top of them really fast as well
Kind of the matchups unbeatable. It's as it's so true stark. I've all the time like there's certain things that happen
We play our old meta against it
It absolutely does not work because of just how high power everything isn't stark up to and for a while
We just complain that it is completely broken and impossible to play as time goes on
We kind of figure it out sometimes maps will change sometimes not as we kind of liberate now sometimes path
Patch is will happen as well, but for the most part. It's a lot of us
It's a lot of us just realizing how you have to play with that and that being said
Thankfully the Oracle will still always be relevant as
Especially in this lazy boy. Yeah, it does get a little bit of her ass there
But I was gonna say right now in pvz
It has to be a two base all in or you go for a mega fast third to try and deal with that
Zerg especially if they do two hatch before spawning pull and in this case we can see it is going to end up being a fast third from
Hero and I'm really happy to see that I think these games have been cool today
We haven't had a lot of macro
No, not too many games have actually managed to make the distance of a long game
So I can Oracle comes in doesn't do quite as much damage the second queen is still there and
A lot of queen coverage with a spore in the natural to keep snoot nice and safe total workers killed nine
Total working units tab by the way 60 some
Look at that units tab
Talk to me Zerg five Zerglings five queens 63 drones and
And that is that's that's part of what's the tough thing about
Produst right now a lot of people again. What's difficult to match up?
Well if you go for a fast third and a Zerg is on top of it like we see from snoot
They will be so minimalist about everything else and they will just plow up to 75 drones and then show up with a very
Difficult like roach ravager link timing attack or if you and if you're not ready for that by the way
Just die or they just it's continue their tech on to hide so that's what's nice about the Oracle opening
We should see hero completely on top of this if you start to see units pouring out in a fourth base taken
He should be in position to try and do something about that
Yep, he's got a lot of gateways. He's going into blink plus one attack meanwhile roaches
Speed upgrade is both close finishing Zergling speed finishing up as well
Warpism always a nice choice sort of buy some time push the Zerg player back these oracles see this building hatch immediately
I think it's yeah, I was gonna say his worm it immediately started attacking the prank to cancel it
Maybe he still will be able to oracles that's crazy amount of damage
Out this this night is warm is so brilliant. I love it. Why I was noticing that there's no upgrades
So I was saying okay, this is gonna be a timing attack and that's cool
That's really tough to deal with it should be ravager roach link but with this night is warm
He's gonna attach something like I mean there's three more queens coming on. So what is this 11 queens? Oh
He said eight he's at eight queens right he's gonna go straight to 11 queens and with all of those
There's obviously no airplay that's gonna work against this
No, is he gonna build ravagers with this which is pretty much there's no reason not to I mean
Maybe he doesn't because he knows something I don't but just ravager not that expensive and they they add so much
There we go. We see for their Oracle in control is correct once again as hero try step out of the map
He has his Oracle tagging the army, but when you see this many queens like what's going through your mind?
I well he doesn't know Snoop very well, so I don't know that he necessarily knows it's an attack just yet
He is gonna pull back and that is the right choice because he centers. Well, maybe he's not pulling all the way back
We's pulling back a little bit links talkers out here cool. They can they have to be careful of zerglings
Of course, but otherwise they can do a little bit of damage kind of feel out what's coming and then back away
I think the Oracle tagging is really useful as well
It's trying to put those queens in the night is he'll see the night is just just that alone right?
I don't know if he's spotted yet. No, he hasn't this Oracle won't
Shouldn't make it outside of the natural
It might oh no, nope
So now the tag is still lasting on a few of these he can build a night is for reinforcements or try to do like a
Backstab with it while he pushes. I don't know. He doesn't have vision actually. No, I'm fair
Hey, so the night is right there right in his face the links run up to the stalkers
He's trying to get on top of those as well, but using the cross-bottom knock on the pylons
And this is so smart like it's right up in his face
There's gonna be creep there is gonna drop a couple of tumors immediately. He's just continuously adding more ravagers
And this is a four-base timing attack that the fourth base is not saturated at all
It's basically a ruse or just purely for production
But these centuries again
This is something that we aren't really seeing in the PVC map like a lot of people's kind of given up on because
Lirkers are so strong against them, but in this case
Centuries can actually hold us off for a while
Yeah, I mean you can use that cross-bottom to break those down
But that means it's not using the aggressive
I'm weird
Like night is in your face. I mean does it give vision?
No, I'm just thinking you'd be able to crack this ramp and get up there and then be able to
Really read I love the defensive states of sport though. He tries to run up front by the you know
We're so far so good. He's he's not dying and he's getting disruptors out which we're gonna give a lot more firepower versus army
Yeah, he's making two at a time too, which is really powerful and as you said
He's actually hold like his unit count is fairly high hasn't lost a lot
He has all these pylons for I guess options
But for the most part, he don't have that many foot to no retards anymore
And the thing is the purification of also works against buildings
So he can use it to cover might as two
He's getting a little bit ahead of himself. You need to be careful with the disruptor great micro here from snoot as well
And he is gonna circle around but his army's quite dwindled and we don't see a return just yet of the night is where my don't think
No, so I feel like snoot. Yeah, he's he's kind of spiritually given up on this. It's gonna back away
And he's got a lot of catching up to do like the fourth base immediately goes down for hero
But tech wise he's in such a good spot with this disruptor coming up. Yeah, he has that of revelation of course
You can still see where snoot's army is he knows I think seeing the links is super important too because he knows he's not gonna
Get back stabbed by moving out of the map without him being able to see that so he can confidently step forward
He is going pretty far deep on to creep but there's the guardian shield popped first
Shrub from bone. I was about to say here's such a good job being patient with it's disruptors
And then I'm like so far to creep but the prison gets into the main base during all this as well
So he's got a bunch of add-outs. He's gonna use that
They shifted move over into the natural expansion and he continues to press the front
Yeah, such good play from hero here, and this is this is where he's just a special player like there were
Roaches to try and run down these add-ups
But snoot just kind of didn't see them for a few seconds huge
Shrub truck goes off on the front lines a second one triggered as well
And he's just blown everything up out of those instructors. This is that's disgusting
It's new to having just a tough time dealing with the all fronts of this attack. It's going on inside the base
It's here. Stu finally does clean up what's going on inside his main base
But it's fourth base is not very saturated
It's just gonna die and the prison is here so he can reinforce directly into the fight as the ravagers
Used their corrosive bile on the front line
So a bunch more stalkers get brought into the fray and those disruptors shots way too good
Hero takes game number one against snoot what a beautiful game
And that's one of those games where I really like snoot's decision making
I thought he had a really good opening very economically sound
Was savvy and knowing that hero was not gonna be able to harass him so he just shot all the 75 drones
I want to ask you do you think like I'm trying to see because it didn't look like he built me Phoenix
Let me finish my point the real quick cuz I don't want to just say snoot did a great job
I'm really okay cuz I am really curious about some yeah, yeah
I what I'm gonna say though is that snoot had a good timing attack planned as well
I don't think there's necessarily a flaw there. This is just kind of a cool example of hero just playing
Exceptionally well he didn't get lucky in the build. He didn't have a huge dark-temper counter attack
He just controlled his army so well
He deflected that attack and snoot was was just kind of outhandled back at home. Go ahead
Do you think the the push itself was meant to be directly at the front cuz or was it was there like something called like he didn't because he didn't
Use an overseer. He didn't have any overlords by together the night is into the main base of the natural and I feel like the biggest thing that
Worked in favor of him was fighting on that ramp because you can force field amount like and not I'm not sure if snoot wanted to go for a
Night-is elsewhere, but
I think you're on something the thing is like I really do feel like a lot of produce players
Crumple to that attack they either take too fast of a fourth or they bleed out too many stalkers and they a lot of them
Don't have centuries by the way, which is kind of a weird point to make most
The philosophy has really been well corrosive by a crushes force fields
But what ends up happening is as long as you're not losing units you are delaying the zerg like every time they have to do a
Voli of corrosive biodes just stop the force fields
They're not surging forward. They're waiting for the corrosive bio to come back as well
It's not waiting that long but enough time for the protest to continue to survive
Yeah, and even then I think it's so pretty interesting because a lot of a lot of zerg players
You like look at it and like well how the decision making breakdown?
It's like well if you use like your corrosive biodes and then they step out and try to attack you once you break the force fields like
You're not just breaking the force field so that you can try to attack
You're also breaking the force field so that they can push into an army that has no corrosive bios
So it's I guess it's like a really awkward thing
We're like you'd rather wait out the force fields and not miss your chance. I think you crush them still
But it's just it's an interesting kind of new element to PVC like it used to be force field throughout
Well, there's nothing I can do so of course I wait now. It's well I can crush those
But in doing so are my zerglings up against it am I hurting them as well?
Do I want to move forward is it too early to move forward?
So it's kind of we're gonna have to figure it out back and forth and see if it is maybe you're right
Maybe you don't crush them and you wait I guess it's obviously situational
But just I have so much respect right here as play like I know so many pro does that in the midst of that the philosophy is
Well, I have to have a war person on their base warping and I need to just I need to get some return on them because otherwise
They're saturating forth while applying pressure
But hero just had such he lost like no stalkers like almost at all
In that frontal push and he just had a big enough army that he was like, oh, you know what?
I can push forward and snoot gave up on it with no upgrades behind it and no drones at the fourth and that was that was kind of the
Yeah, especially the point about no upgrades
There's not a lot of longevity to that style no matter what you do and I don't think
It's not very well set up for any other type of follow-up like into really do damage anything of that sort okay
Got everybody in the lobby now and we are ready to go second map larylite crest
I mean this
Can we say this I mean in my mind I assume this is a zerg favorite mappagans produce
I mean I mean you have two you have two ramps yes into your natural neither ramp can be blocked by three buildings
So I just in my brain my first thought is it's too hard to wall. It's tough
It's a it can end up being a good blink stalker map, but also blink stalker and PVZ is in a weird spot where like if you get the right
Composition that you're facing it can be fantastic
But students been doing a good job of adding lanes having roaches and ravager and that composition is very difficult for blink stalkers because
One bad blink they're all gone. They're absolutely all gone and the map's not big enough to make up the difference in time for that too
All right, let's find out it's a cross-pons
So at the very least a little extra distance between the two and in the bottom left
We have it's newt our red zerg player another question mark. I you know what just you know
I'm gonna give the benefit of the doubt. I'm gonna assume that the
RPCs or something I think it might be like a special character
That the starcraft engine or whatever doesn't show okay
I know that if you type a symbol that they can't display her for whatever reason it shows up as a question mark
Okay, I like I tried to put some copypastas in game before and it just showed up as question marks
I'm gonna assume that was it you are the dank name scientist
You would know we have to test these things in the top right of course. I currently leading one oh
CJ enters his hero
Best of five as we've had all night so I'm excited game one ended with a
Overwhelming Krodos victory like just crushing down
But the execution of the two players was really something beautiful. I love snooze strategy
I loved him punishing the pro-dots for his opening
I like the idea behind the timing attack and then it put here on a position where it's like all right hero
Show us your micro and I'll tell you what hero is one of the best players in planet earth and a big part of the reason for that is because of his micro
Like he of course is strong and all categories of starcraft, but I
Love watching him. He was one of the guys leading that bling stalker revolution in PVC towards the end of heart of the swarm as well
Right. Oh, yeah, yeah, absolutely. I mean MC. I think was like the grandfather of that so many of his games
Ended with just a wave of bling stalkers, but here was the guy that at the Kespa top level kind of brought in
Though like actually if you control these really well, you can kill basically anything and it was actually kind of boring for a little while
Because it's like guys. Please get better at dealing with bling stalkers. Yeah, I'm like winning too many games
I want to I am catavita or no, that was actually SOS that one of the finals
But anyways heroes got to the finals basically off of bling stalkers in all three matchups as the primary opening
Difference in openings this time around obviously no faster pace. There's nothing at that third yet for snoot
But it's going for the fast-link speed and I think we just kind of talked about why or at least I was contemplating why I feel this map
Bavors zerg to some extent is that you have this opening and the way the wall is done
You have two ramps that lead into your natural and they're both very wide
You know, this is like this would be your main ramp on a map like ruins of Saras something like that and then this map
This ramp is obviously just very very large
So since you can get into both sides walling it off is very difficult. You have to start your wall here
I mean, I feel like run by something that you see almost everything from zerg on this map
It's an expensive wall in it
I mean, it's a three gateways at best at the large one and then if you wall in that other ramp
I don't know
I mean a lot of people try to go over the rocks try to knock those down
But with a two-base speedling opening like this if you try that it's very likely you don't end up knocking this rock sound instead
Get a flood of zerglings
But also something to think as you're talking about off-stream as well is the prevalence now of drop-length something
We've seen for sure but eight speed zerglings in your main base if you don't have a pound or perhaps you have only one
Yeah, all of a sudden photon overcharges are not nearly as prevalent as well because they're higher cost
So yeah, I've been especially keeping an eye on snooze infrastructure
He hasn't built an evolution chamber and he also didn't mind the 25 gas necessary to make a drop over Lord
Okay, his speedlings do catch this
It's gonna barely stay on a transfer just in the last second. There's the overloads
Of course it's 25 minerals 25 gas and suddenly if he comes a drop over Lord
That's a cool long by the way like that
Instead of walling off both the ranch is going for the next this this right here is pretty much what we're just talking about
These elings are gonna be a constant threat in that natural expansion as he's gonna have to leave some space open to get units out of his base
Hey, just I don't transfer that. Okay. Oh
We keep seeing these friendly this keeps happening interactions like I could have killed them
But guess not more links coming out, but also drones for snooze
So it doesn't look like it's gonna be necessarily just a speedling all in
He does have as we can see here the score crawler as well and the there's a oracle gonna get a couple of kills
But for the most part not as much as it would like
Nope, he's quite a few of its hit points as well
There's still a lot of links out on the map overall worker count is favoring hero
You just continue to hold on against this there's four addips inside that natural expansion
But a couple of probes are gonna get knocks down and I like that from snooze by the way like
Losing zerglings is so not a big deal as long as something's happening and and I say that very
Specifically like if they're scouting that's worth 50 or 100 minerals
That's that's kind of what Terrence pay with with scans. It's kind of what proto-pay with like observers and hallucinations kind of
But zerglings if they can get a few probes and information
Holy Toledo we're talking about good stuff
Yep, now with that Stargate play of course being followed up a couple of Phoenix to help pitch in
Resonating glaves coming in dealt for the add-up so he's gonna get that 45% attack speed boost makes him a lot better versus
Zergling especially when they get surrounded
Is that a complete wall in with the natural?
No, okay, you're the proto-paying no, he's got space right there at the gas
So almost a complete wall and he'll probably leave behind an add-up
But I feel like we're about to see
Too-based timing attack and it's gonna be very add-up heavy, which is gonna be super interesting
Because a lot of times people do that with Oracle back up
But there's just this odd pair of Phoenix going around and a third and a fourth coming out as well
And this is part of the tough time with with Stargate openings like
They're coming up very slowly the Zerg knows to make a bunch of drones. So maybe heroes like so incredible that he's
Trying to trigger that but here all is really good
So I can't I can't say that that's the kind of thing that would blow me away
We do have roaches coming out now for snooze, but are they gonna be enough?
You know all these questions coming in he's waiting on four overlords right now to complete before he can actually build any more units
Well unfortunately for him though like this is the this is a mega old reference
But for those of you that watch like Tsl and Mondragon back in the wings of Liberty days
There was a counter chart and it was Phoenix's while you counter with roaches
And that's exactly what's happening here. There's no drones coming out. Snooze is not being tricked. So these Phoenix
They're they're pretty okay against ravagers. So I assume that's what he's hoping to do with these
But again here comes a bunch of queens is snooze just gonna knight us worm and back up the ravagers. Oh wow
He's just gonna face you should tell port right inside of his face. There's actually no units. Okay
There are some roaches here he picks up some of the queens in the back
I mean trying to get the ones with the most energy of course
Gonna help a lot is gonna teleport all of his add-its away from the spike boss possibly as the next wave comes in
He's like yep, okay, we're gonna start playing ring around the Rosie
They get all the queens. I mean there are roaches here so that the add-its themselves not gonna do much
But the Phoenix kill all the queens without really losing anything. That's a pretty decent trade if I might say so myself
For the photos player and the Phoenix are still chipping away quite a bit at this some of the add-its do escape
He warped some in the home to defend the link counter attack and I like this because he's taken the other third base as well
So he doesn't have that prime position
To get any damage done. Yeah, this is huge. He's just dealing with all these add-its is constantly running around his base
Picks off another queen
Slap in these drones and of course you mentioned it without the queens
I mean these features can just dance around all day and they're at critical mass like they don't care about a single sport
Caller anymore. They're picking up all the queens like this
This is unfolding before a snooze eyes. He's like what is going on? I had eight queens
Why am I all of a sudden losing the Phoenix?
What was because of that add-up backup and behind this the third base is being taken the Phoenix count continuing to crawl up?
By the way, so unless there's gonna be Hydras or something
These can actually affect like you can't make ravagers against this they will just kill every ravager
Yeah, and you can see the dark shrin is on the way as well. He's looking for that finishing blow
Of course, I think he realized there's no layer yet for snooze
He does finally have this is ugly up. Yeah, I mean you've got this many Phoenix just killing roaches
You know you're in a bad spot, is there well snooze behind this is is is droning up
So it's not the end of the world, but he's just now taking his fourth
He's not really tacked up. You'll notice evolution chambers coming out
But on that production tab we don't see upgrades like there's the first upgrade. There's the layer snooze has been
I mean, he's just been stagnated beyond belief. He's in such a bad spot right now
Yeah, and you know here
It is constantly looking for things to kill you manage to scrub another queen
He's gonna go for another one and this is isn't care. It's gonna go one after another
I mean was that sport probably saves the other two queens and other ones
Just amazing amazing Phoenix control here from here
Like just the way he set himself up and as you have the adips at the front is pulling the roaches away
He's really just distracting him and he gets another queen
And this queens you don't want to probably too far forward as well here coming the adips snooze not really reacting to this
He's still fighting them over at the fourth another
He's beautiful. No really solid play no one checks no anti air
He can even help if he wanted to try if he had the energy to pick up some roaches while these adips come in killing more drones
I'm in love with the synergy between the adip and the Phoenix though like each time the adips showed another base
These Phoenix are picking up one or two maybe three roaches this style is so cool
You know this is like this is like a rotty builder something. You know so little just it's kind of out there, you know a little bit
Phoenix Phoenix adips just feels a bit odd now. He's okay. He's mixing some immortals now the blink is coming in
But what an interesting, you know way of picking opponent or a Ford arc Templar
zerks
join hands and
Continue and prepare to bathe yourselves and the salty salty tears. I mean there's two sport cars
That's going for snoot here and he is reacting fairly quickly not gonna be able to pick off. So okay never run
Yeah, but that big a class for your hands you get saved the tears. He doesn't manage to save the dTs
That pickup range on the warp prison, but he's taking a fifth which should be a fourth base
snoot's been battered more warp gates finishing snoot has managed to make it to investors
So I'm guessing he's trying to use fungal to lock down the Phoenix for ravager shots or lock down the adips
Yeah, I mean lock down anything I guess at this point, but second robo robotics bay like the game's kind of evolving past
snoots snoots to up the mid game aspect like the investors are gonna be a nice thing
But again, investors have a tough time with Phoenix like if they can't land a critical fungal and there's not a decent enough number of queens to finish them off
It won't be enough
DTs get dropped once again one of them does get these two just right. Yeah, Kelly more queens
Can you show me how?
I'm actually ready to show I don't actually don't think this overlay has that button. Yeah
And someone someone tell us is this is a game of regicide man
There's there I would venture a guess it's over 20 as a lot of dead Queens
Six investors are on the way. He's like basically praying at this point
This will end the Phoenix madness and I love the fourth base timing attack behind this or not time anyways
The fourth base timing behind this the Phoenix give him ultimate information
snoot is is being conditioned to
Defend he's back at home. He's like fairly holding on
He's making units, but these units are not to attack there to survive and by the time he gets out of his base like he might even
uggle all these things good for him. He needs to
But he doesn't have the anti-air to finish these guys off
So yeah a couple of Phoenix die. There's the good fungles. This is nice
But the world outside of snoots base has evolved beyond him. It's it's double disruptor
It's there's immortals out there. There's blank stalkers. There's an equal base pro dust
That's knocking on the door of your fourth base. This is a very treacherous place to be. Yep the immortal stalker army shows up
He's got DT's makes him with this as long as you mentioned those disruptors. He can recall out he wants
He's gonna throw that
Pervocation over grabs one of the investors in a few roaches
He steps back double time. What's gonna be dropped to help I guess create a slow
Oh god, it's so slow now. Just gonna feed everything at all. Try to dodge the disruptors then
And hero
This is a thing of beauty like this is your future pro dust in the hands of a good player. This is what it looks like and
Hero is just he's just man handling snoot in a very very surgical kind of way like
snoots up and supply
He's re-adding his fourth base so I'm not ready to call him dead just yet
But man is this gonna be enough bill battle for him sending a lot to counter attack against that third base trying to get some work on
What is this like what a weird look at this couple of I mean
It's a very he knows dark temple are out there. So I mean it's a it's a motley assort
It's very important to say the least he just dives on time just blinks right on top of his okay
Just kill these same approach and then go back home and kill you
I think he's free of supply. He wants to I mean he's adding the ultra's cavern and he I think he's also buying time
He's like hey go back to your base and defend for a minute like leave me alone
If he can get ultra-sout it's it's not so bad. There is three immortals out there
But again ultra-s in legacy the void are different they are
Nyan stop will we do a storm coming in are they I just had a curiosity because I'm not sure they really don't know how are they the same though like for
ZVP
Immortals still do a good job if you have enough right they they dictate composition
I mean if you have four plus immortals you're okay. You're okay
They're strong, but they're not like they are in TV's where there's like basically no answer all right
Well, I guess a nice disruptor attack. It's great for raffles there
As well and heroes just really starting to just lay into them now those instructors really getting some key shots
He has vipers so you could go for the the blinding clown fungal combination of doom
Well, let's be fair here
I've been pretty down on snoop, but here he goes great up ducks
We certainly actually cut into that immoral count just before we start to see some ultra-s
But again hero is gonna surge back
There's been a little bit of a defensive line set up here
Zerglings are quite a bit more powerful for us
Cute up as well
And there's the kindness plating that the downside is his upgrades are again quite lackluster
But to be fair so are heroes heroes are not great at all
He's got some temple already to move forward now storm finishes up
So he can storm you can feedback. He has he has options. He has choices at this point
He's gonna step in starting to attack these spine crawlers looking for some
Foot hole is he gets a feedback off killing one of the investors continues to step forward and this fourth base of snoop
It's like it's gonna get knocked down
He's got the dt's in here as well
If I see you down a lot this the preemptive storm is just saying yeah come at me come on down
There's another fungal he does hit a good number of these units
He gets a blinding clock too is the ultra-six pop but the immortals are not under that blinding clock
If you can just focus though then he should be able to get them the purification
It was also helps shred those ultra-six and hero killing the ultra is I mean that there that's there's nothing else
It is so fun to watch in place our crap like that was how we control that army that was not a name
Move place and gentlemen that's this is not mundane pro-dose that just wins the game for itself
That was a hand crafted victory from hero over one of the absolute best foreigners who is not playing bad
By the way the scores two and oh, but I'm impressed with snoot snoot had his moments in time in both these games where I
Think he was really testing the limits of hero, but man
That here. This is scary stuff from here. He's playing so well really really good play
I mean the stalker controls from the phoenix adept play just blew my mind
I have I have seen mass adept sort of styles on larylach in most matchups
But I haven't seen it paired that well with a really heavy phoenix composition in the way that he controls both at the same time
It's like he's playing our con mode with himself or something
Well, it comes down to a critical moment in time because there definitely is kind of a critical mass of queens versus phoenix
Obviously if you somehow had 40 phoenix it doesn't matter how many queens you have for the most part
But that's not the case you had like seven or eight
And he was facing eight or so queens if those queens could kind of see what was coming and it was like oh god
These adeps are face shifting on top of my queens with the phoenix outside of sport crawler range
And there's no roaches there if all those things fall into place
It's an amazing moment time for hero and he's able to really take that advantage and run with it
but
There's so many times where no one's that bold with the adeps
There is a sport crawler or two there and it really only takes one or two and if that fight goes the way of snoot all the sudden
He has four bases. He has ravagers. He's getting up the high
He can turn that game around and I will say though
He you know, aside from all the damage that he took snoot did a really good job of actually getting to that tech like yes
You consider the beating he took he still managed to get out investors
Vipers and Ultralisks. I'm telling you that that fight that kind of determined the game over at the fourth base over there
I feel like
I feel like if hero doesn't control that as well as he does
He obviously doesn't just die. He has four bases behind that. He's he's got great tech
He's an okay shape, but I feel like snoot takes the advantage
I really do and I feel like a lot of produce would miss handle that fight
But the disruptor shots on top of all the Ultralisks kind of navigating outside of the blinding clouds
controlling the stalkers as well as he did just everything on top of everything was just so well played
Yeah, we're loaded into what could be the last yeah no question mark from my from our produce this game
He's just yet maybe someone like message him. He's like yeah, you know, the next doesn't show up anymore
Oh, okay, it's supposed to be like my my he's like a emoji that he likes because like actually emoji doesn't work in the Starcraft client
Which we should fix
But I in the bottom left he's up to oh this best of five. I like the work fix there. Yeah. Oh, it's a problem for sure broken
Just imagine if if bligh by the way look at this fast speed of a liquid snoo here in the top left
Just imagine if bligh could actually have his clantag be a fire emoji. I
Imagine that world and I don't necessarily think it's any better
But you know, it's fine to each their own the more the barrier and
Just just this map by the way kind of the same problems is laryllic crest for produce in the sense that you can fast
Expand that's a large ramp that ramp is far away from your actual nexus is so if they get past that if they drop past that
You're in a little bit trouble. It doesn't have the double ramp of course a little bit of a different dynamic
Yeah, but as we can see in the thing is pointed out we do see snoo changing it up a little bit
This is a one base rush speed very quick queen coming out at the same time as the original the initial eight links and
Snooge gets lucky here with an overload scout. There's not gonna waste time going anywhere else hero when
Nexus first so a lot of trouble. This should be the ideal scenario for
Absolutely and hero doesn't have a probe out of the map so
Unless his instincts are on some kind of weird god level that we're always like a wizard and we don't know that he's using black magic
To some visions of his opponents builds. He's making his out just now
The cyber-scoors of course can be completely irrelevant. It's gonna try to make you see these links now
His probe season immediately turns around what can you do though?
I mean there's no mother should core coming out anytime relevant. There's no way to defend this nexus is there
There shouldn't be I mean the zealot will pop out and snooge to start working on the nexus. There's no pile on
You should maybe send one lane to go poke up the ramp and see what we're looking at in the second season
But he sees the cyber's court just now finishing snooge right now is feeling good
This is a good feeling for snooge that pounds very little bit
That's annoying this base got to feel nice. He's he starts a hatchery for himself or he's gonna pull probes
Hero desperate to save this base bringing probes on to help for this zealot
But the zealot gets picked up very quickly second zealot comes down
Mother should core is out
It's got to be so careful this photon over charge. He really does pulling probes. What a what a madman
Add up is about to come out the add up would add in a big way
Snoot is adding a hatchery behind still links he hasn't killed a lot of damage. He hasn't killed any probes either like so now he's
He's in is this is this worst case scenario for snooge that he actually bad
This is a really rough spot to be and he's gonna run around for a natural try to get on top of the adept in his elephant
There's the overcharge probes gonna block off the top with a pile on
Beautiful play from hero and I think snooge all was so to realize he's still to build links
He's like oh crap well. He's just gonna try to flood this but I
Mean letting that pile on finishes is gonna haunt his dreams if this continues to go the way it is so far
I just gonna try to move into that mineral line trying to bait these four strong. I guess he wants to bait the overcharge
But until he's not a second one. There shouldn't be a second one. He doesn't have the energy for it
I think he's at something like 40 some energy now. Yeah 43
So he will in a second, but even that here has to be careful because he's basically to have one over charge do something with
It's gonna lose all of his ground force. Hey, let's sell these ground forces get surrounded out here
That's a whiff oh
He gets my the edges made it into the base of hero and the probes are getting pulled back in the opposite direction
But this is that's got to be it right should be end game moments here
We're starting to see probes die in droves. He's in on the face. There's no pile in there. You should go for that
That's huge. No kill the pilot. I mean, he's gonna win no matter what man that pile is a big deal. It stops
Okay, that's fine. Wow
There's no coming back for that pile on that stops warp gate stops an adept coming out for the for the best of five
You know that game aside
This matchup gets pretty weird now because we have central protocol in Oren 11
central protocols the next map
And that's a weird map. It's very large has a lot of the problems we've been talking about
Just multiple entryways into a large ramp distance from the Nexus so kind of
Well, so I mean snoot definitely nice
They basically the build order win right there, right?
He goes for this super fast speedling rush versus a Nexus first on a map where defending that natural is so difficult
There's no easy way to wall it off
And here almost did by the way like I was
Lings went back and like wait is he really basically Nate if he has a probe on that ramp like he did originally and just
What if he has the sublet's the pile and finish there?
It's still bad because he was able to circle around the two adips in the zeal and kill it and there was no photo
Recharge because he snapped did it at the natural yeah, which was a little bit of a mistake from here
We should have waited and see where the zealings are commit
Zerg is so fast of course the best case scenario unless snoot makes a huge mistake is he puts it at the ramp
He loses two zealings goes into the natural and has free reign there
So it's not like hero made a huge mistake
But of course we saw the secondly went in the main that was game. Yeah, that was game. He's all over
I mean you said it as well
You could have a pile on that head warp gate researching some great spots for snoot as he
Get some stuff in map scorts two to one now favoring CJ and his hero if you wins this map on central protocol
He will advance eliminating student he will play against SOS
That's I think so as first hero tell us all this time probably the
two best pro I mean there's gonna be someone that's gonna be like Jeff you
Someone will disagree with you so just be forced not the best but they're definitely in contention guys
I think we can agree yeah very good players
We are loaded in to central protocol and I mean I don't get to see very many games on this
You know most matches the star capture played in best of three so you know
It's one of the unique parts of the best of five is whether or not these players like maps like this
Hey, these maps get vetoed out of every single best of three. They are gonna have to play them and we're gonna have to see them try to
Make some magic as it were and just as a fan of Starcraft actually I do like that
I mean I've been to those MLG's
You like watching players. Oh my god watching those players being uncomfortable positions. What's what?
I mean yeah, I think Starcraft is a game especially in Starcraft 2 where it can become very
Meta-laden and very like this is what we all do and the games look very similar but on these weird maps
You got a dip into your bag of your own creativity and come out with something new
Bask out here for hero as he sees snooze base of course snooop atop right and hero in the bottom right
We get these vertical spawns again, so I think that rush this since very very short. Is this a road-ravider play?
I mean he's going to gateway so I'm assuming
Just fast adept and trying to crush his opponent early on
I mean like I'm in the same boat as you man. I've this is probably my first professional PVC
I've seen on this map so yeah, I haven't I haven't cast like any games on this one except the only thing already today
So I'm excited
I'm excited for our own enjoyment and I relish in their pain unfortunately
Both these players would tell you they're like no, I don't believe this yeah, I don't know what's going on
No, let's see. I guess this is where you break out your beta builds, right?
It's like well this worked in the legacy of the void beta
So maybe I can just rush out a bunch of adepts. He's still gonna expand though that crow boost is on the gateway
There's nothing being made it is obviously a slight
I guess he's waiting right is like I don't want to build any probes so might as well just wait for the current on the adept
You know that millisecond that millisecond in control where he clicks on the gateway
It starts to add up to then corno's it. You know that's not enough. It's just not perfect playing it
So just look at that alternating the chrono
So that they finish at the same time in control. Is that not TLO tier of creative?
Well, I've basically already
Gushed over here as much as I'm allotted as a caster. That's amazing
Because otherwise the other one would have finished too early and then you can't do much with just one attempt
Well, you can do a lot, but I mean I do as much answer your question. I love it. Thank you Jeff
It's just if I guess too much of a player it becomes well, I mean you can't tell me that I'm right
You can't just tell me I'm right all the time and you know bad things at
Yeah, there's no queen here yet. So these addicts could get a bit of work done. They're gonna do some work
I mean it's just a lings and a queen anyways
Yeah, they're gonna say there were drones and the natural you could have gone for there was no queen there
Just trying to pick up a few drones. I like this. You throw that shade out you get ready for
Teleport out and yeah, I mean the queen is done now
So we'll get as much but four drones. Maybe if he focuses he gets a fifth
Obviously bare bones is worth it, but just keep in mind as well that he basically he made some sacrifices to get those two out
So certainly they were worth it. I'm not trying to argue that they aren't they got great intel killed five drones
And slow down the Zerg in general with this many links though coming out and speed being done his natural completely open
Just give another like we said giant ramp no pylon here's a bit of a mistake
You just have a mother ship or either he just has a couple of attents and he's gonna go ahead that poor out of to get back to the boat time
Jimmy no
He is adding by the way a toilet council behind this return. Did he cancel it or finish finish?
That's mega that's weird and I'm guessing he was gonna try to do like two base add-on
Making the most required the wrong this is just the thing. This is this man. It gets up. Okay, right?
He just has that that resistance unbelievably short unfortunately
We're looking at hero not knowing what to do on a map like this. This is what he came up with
It's like mega fast one has has hero played a best of five yet in ZVP and legacy the way
I don't even know I would be surprised if he did
So you just gonna want to pump the brakes and links right now. He's played this
Oh, he's dropped the phone. I mean, this is another thing that you know, that's the wrong ramp
That's not it
Confusing in his defense. He's still got links on both sides resonating glades on the ways well for those edits
Yeah, he's like okay just run around anyway. Everybody do it. I guess this is the one way that's new can mess us up
Nope, no, it might he gets around and
Parallels gonna get overcharged
It gets to be fights here. That's okay. He's giving your chance and what the rush is so short
You don't even need great to move your queens across the map. He's like, you know what?
I guess I'm kind of committed right? I think you saw a 12 counts well, wait because you just had four crawlers
So he's like it's very gonna get DT. It's very forward of you. This feels like a game
I should win am I gonna get DT feels like I'm watching Fancy here at that MLG you were talking about bro
That's a throwback
He was great. He's a fun sir. He played with like the combat helmet on yeah, that part was weird, but his style of players cool
Old two reference for those and these are going to drop right now
Yep, I mean he's gonna try to just what teleport all these out of side get the queens
The links aren't here and he does have add up the tax speed upgrade done
I think the bot's dropped definitely hurt quite a bit
But yeah, these out of some when the links come back they just get all over and he can drop these links in the main base to
He will they're actually gonna go the whole way. I love this. I mean you he couldn't make like the thing is in the beta
You were never sure because there was no different model for the overlord right?
Wow, that is
To be fair there was Adam's below it so it's night the circling is wrong
Yeah, they were on the teeth of the overly like I know we jump brothers in the beta
There was no separate model for the drop overlord so you weren't sure but I'm like who are you trying to fool snow like I don't know
Maybe just scouting overlords the queens do die like if you had banelings in it and he's like
I'm just gonna drop banelings and make him think this drop is empty and it's like okay
By the way, how many drones we looking at that natural not a lot. Okay total work counts 27 to 24 hero is ahead
I still feel like there's a lot of lost opportunities with the failed drop that he the very first one where he just
Droped them outside of his base and then he could have run them into the main. Oh, yeah, he he didn't so no
I mean if if Snooze goes on to lose this game
He will this these are the kind of losses that feel super bad
Especially considering that his match point if you're a win this one trying to get through this century though
It does he does very good. Another force field comes down
Still not doing anything that's why I count so I guess he was considering going for some other type of aggressive play
But just didn't have the opportunity and all of a sudden there's add-ups which actually with those ugly
It's dying or they could be mega mega annoying. There are roaches out so of course in a stand-up fight
The roaches would win but the questions can't oh, oh, he canceled a weird choice. He canceled all but to I guess trying to
Stipe drones, but maybe he wasn't thinking about what there were roaches right there. I mean he must have not been looking man
It's tough spot the fool
But he does see he sees roaches coming out and by the way adds an immortal well
I mean I killed my punchline there it is anyway
It's a robo to make a mortals and on low-e-consituations and mortals with centuries are gods by the way absolute gods
Well, he's going to say for a robo bay. So they're not gods when they don't exist though
Well, I mean you can stop appreciate you so appreciate you can't you can work even if they're
Not there the worship the thought of them
Hero it's finally got that natural mining. It's got to feel good
She's gonna teleport a bunch of add-ups inside since cancel the shade and that's the one that actually would have done something
I guess he's a one to commit them because we have a
Rager he's I mean snutes getting ready for a follow-up all of them that looks like the immortal is coming out too
By the way, so I'm guessing he just wants to get a quick disruptor to follow this up and hero is not showing the centuries yet
Now several centuries were spotted the natural of course when the certainly tried to run by so snute remembers
He knows they exist needs to be very careful about this round
Now he's also burned out one of these folks in overcharges
He can only afford to do one more so his ability to defend an attack
This is substantially limited. There's the first force was gonna try to lock these units
And he has that immortal of course it does not do bonus damage to the ravager
But killing those is still of utmost importance the barrier helping to soak up a lot of the heat
Actually without the lingering reinforcements the immortal is able to do a lot of work on these roaches
Just needs to keep cut microing it back and next overcharge really helping out as well. Yeah
Yeah, he's a very decisive victory again in a low-eat concentration like this
You can see snute already going to plan B. There's the guys or there's the drones and again
Unfortunately for snoot because of those force fields and because of how well hero executed that defense
Snoot's not going back to much. He has no upgrades. He's no layer
They're now on equal bases like this is this game is collapsing around snoot and with disruptors coming out in a war prism
We're about to see a show a firework show
Yeah, this is this is what's really gonna set him up for our great spot
Of course the disruptors are just so good against this for the army without layer
You have no road speed so good luck dodging those purification
No, this is gonna try to teleport much addent and I don't
Whatever man
Keep doing that great intel
Keep snoot occupy like snoots can what snoot has to do to control the defense of that
Far in a way is more than what heroes do here's I'm looking just like I'm gonna cancel this the last second
Boop
It's very nice because he that that shows up on your mini map
You know he sees like oh units are coming. Okay. I gotta be prepared and if you don't control by don't move my units
He could just let them finish yeah, and then you go you let some finishes like yeah
Did you think I'm not paying attention? He's gonna come in to sign the queen?
That shade back the other way and oh, okay really nice person bounce all right snoot
Three of them four
So actually good for snoot in that situation. I do you like a year old taking a third base not willing to commit to it
Just a complete two-base push. He's still building disruptors. I'm surprised he hasn't added in a
Warp prism to help with
In a solve well keep in mind. This is a 10 minute game actually it looks like it's minute seven or six or something like that
But it's it's 10 there is a whole aggressive opening stage
So the third base is actually really smart because pro-doss falls off the face of the earth economically the second
They hit one base. It's like so bad what you can produce with that
But two bases that's kind of our that's our happy that's our happy ground
We can make everything we want with that. It's not forever. Yeah, I mean enough champions
Going off that for me to know that uh-huh and
Overlord is kind of moving around. Maybe some of the probies gonna check you should be able to spot this
Painling nest and the links on the way so students all in he's got to go for it and
Unfortunately the tough part about that is he's leveraging against heroes micro like all leaning against heroes like
It's like of all the people that you could try to do this against you're going against one of these guys
It just has such a phenomenal micro
But I guess you know the map kind of put us in this awkward spot where we had that mega aggressive play and then it's led into
This low economy situation where neither player you know are having an easy time getting past a hundred supply
Well here's defense man. That's why we're here like
Snoot
Against most pro-doss this game is over and snoot is easily won but hero
Spot back to this and all of a sudden hero isn't the commanding position. There's overlord speed
Yeah, this this matches truly just been a testament to heroes resolution in these scenarios
He's done so well now coming up with these instructors. He throws up this verification of his oh don't get on three ravagers
picks off another one
And two more I love it. It's just one at a time so good take your time
Very patient play out of enemy cells those force fields as well killing the ravagers of course limits the ability to cancel or crush those force fields
Yeah, and I think he's even nice got a stalker here poking at this third base that snoot wants to take spots the base
But there's a warpers he left his mother ship core at his third base too. So good luck killing that
I mean here is just so on top of this game. There's I'm loving the century play like I cannot wait to go home and start working on my
He's in an incorporating centuries and it did look like you wanted to try to do some bane rain on this army
But picks up his ravagers instead having a hard time deporting those bane lanes. I guess that's I guess snoot
Maybe thinks that he has a chance with that but that's just his only that's yeah, he has no options, right?
So I mean, yeah, you can't be critical of anything snoot does this point time. It's like he's just
He himself is is gotta be just like how did we get here? Why are you still alive?
And he's gonna add bane is he gonna try for a big all-in
But I mean it even in the situation yeah, and four years before you supply more knock on the door. Oh man
Is that powerful army? Yeah, yeah, our cons are a great way to yeah, little Paul through pretty much saw bane links
I mean our cons are fantastic. Yeah, you should see these drop over Lord to maybe consider the possibility of what is about to hit him
But oh god, he's getting so many ravagers with that he's so on top it while while backing up and here come the bane
Links but of course it was no support. That's decent damage. They're gonna be enough
Snoot's got nothing left GG hero wins three to one here in tele extreme masters type A will advance on to play against
SOS and this in my final and score wise
This is not the most intriguing match, but for me
This is the coolest match of the night like I sure I know guys
I've got so much about hero but also tip of that to snoot because this is one of the rare cases where someone loses like three one
But I do not feel like he was just getting
He wasn't getting all he didn't go you know full-forn or make huge mistakes
Or didn't he actually won the build order coin flip in the one game that he won the other games that he lost
He was ahead at certain times or just at least threatening hero with really sound decision making good builds
But unfortunately for him I feel I hope I hope
Despite losing in this first round after flying all the way to type A he goes you know what?
There's more for me to do and learn because here I just put on a clinic up top to your play and soon opened up
Those opportunities for himself as well like that drop he could have had eight links while hero had just three adips blocking that ramp
But you know great play either way hero really showing his resolution in that series and so tomorrow
You guys will have to look forward to as the boys in Taipei
Apollo
Chalaris Todd toward we're bringing you guys the semis and the finals we have
Beyond facing off against soul key SOS playing against here. So some TVZ some PvP
Great matchups and again after seeing the level of play from these guys. I cannot wait. I mean SOS looked incredible hero
Looked all the guys looking incredible. Yeah, that PvP in particular
I'm really excited for because I feel like the MC versus SOS one was was good
But it was kind of one side SOS was anyone two games from just DTs basically murdering him a great execution in game over two
But now I'm excited for those games. It's gonna be great. I'll be watching for sure
That's right and that wraps it up here for us tonight ladies and gentlemen
Thank you so much for tuning in this has been neat and in control from Burbank bringing you guys day one of the
Intellectual Masters Taipei
See you guys tomorrow. He'll be tuned into the semis and the finals on day two